'The number you have
dialled is currently busy.'
'Please try later.'
'The number you have
dialled is currently busy.'
'Please try later.'
'The number you have
dialled is currently busy.'
'Please try later.'
'The number you have
dialled is currently busy.'
'The person you are calling
is speaking to someone else.'
'You can wait or call again later.'
'The person you are calling
is speaking to someone else.'
'You can wait or call again later.'
'The person you are calling
is speaking to someone else.'
'You can wait or call again later.'
'The person you are calling
is speaking to someone else.'
'You can wait or call again later.'
'The person you are calling
is speaking to someone else.'
'You can wait or call again later.'
'The person you are calling
is speaking to someone else.'
'You can wait or call again later.'
Sir.
What's the problem?
Who is she talking to
at this hour?
What is it? Open up, sir.
Ratheesh, don't make me tense.
You can't imagine how worried I'm.
I can understand only if
you tell me why you're worried.
Any problem with your wife?
Are you guys fighting
over something?
'Hi Sweetheart, what's up?'
How long have I been calling you?
- 'Sorry, I didn't see your call.'
To whom were you talking?
- 'I... From Oman...'
At 2.00 am, midnight, huh?
'Sweetheart...I'm...'
- How could you do this to me?
'What have I done to you, honey?'
Did you forget, I bought you
a very costly I-phone?
Since then, you're always online
either on Facebook,
or WhatsApp.
I never get you on call.
'Why do you sound like
a male chauvinist?'
'Dear, when you go to work, I must
pass my time, isn't it?'
Listen Raji, don't try to
make a fool out of me.
'Jaison, you better
speak decently.'
Don't say anything more.
- 'I will say.'
You must be available
whenever I call you.
'If you try to control me,
I will talk back for sure.'
You're messing with a cop.
- 'So what if you're a cop?'
Hello.
How dare she hang up my call?
- Sir.
You should not be so
nasty to your wife.
Too bad.
Whose wife, you mean?
Isn't she your wife?
Are you crazy?
She is just a woman I met
at the station eight months ago.
I'm just having fun with
her, that's all.
And now, she acts like
a faithful wife.
She's talking to her husband
in Oman, now at 2.00 am.
It just turned my mood off.
Buddy…
That thing, right?
What is its name? Er...
G-spot?
- Yeah, G-spot.
What did you just say?
Hey, give me the internet thing.
It's 'Hotspot'.
- Yeah, that 'Pot' itself.
See if it has come.
What's the password?
Aatukalamma.
What?
Aatukaalamma.
What a crappy password,
Ratheesh?
My wife created it for me, sir.
Hurray!
Look at this.
- What is it?
Is it okay?
Wow!
Sir, do you have the seventh clip?
- Which one?
That of Solar Girl?
No, I have a new one.
Sunny Leon.
See if you like it.
Wow! It's HD.
Sir, send it to me, please.
- See the video clarity.
What is it?
- Please send it to me.
You want it?
- Yes.
I can send it to you if you want.
But don't utter my name if my wife
catches you red-handed.
Sir, do you think anyone would
tell your name to his wife?
What are you saying?
Oh, shit, the storage space
is too less.
Yes, it's rotating.
- I have sent it.
Huh, it's rotating, it's rotating.
Sir.
- Pick the call.
'Hello, Ratheesh sir.'
- Hello, sir.
'Have you reached the spot?'
'We are here at the street café,
behind the BSNL quarters.'
'We're on the road to the right
of the same BSNL quarters.'
'Shall we get in, sir?'
But sir isn't it raining
heavily outside?
'Do we have
to bother with the rain?'
'He's online now.'
'If we enter now, we can
catch him right away.'
Yeah, we're coming, sir.
Sir, it's
the fourth house from here.
Sir, follow us.
[Indistinct background voice over]
Hello.
Hey, sir asked you to
meet him upstairs.
Okay.
- Go, quick.
[Indistinct chatter]
Sir.
- What is it?
Aneesh sir, from the Cyber cell
called me here.
What time?
- 'Sir, any updates?'
Yes, the report will be
submitted today evening.
We have informed FEFKA and
Producer's association.
We just need a few updates
from the Piracy squad.
'Sir, please give us
the news first.' - Okay.
'It's for airing an exclusive news.'
Venu, there's a press conference
in the evening.
'I firmly believe in you and...'
Let's discuss the rest
of things there.
'I just need a byte for scrolling.'
- You hang up.
I'll call you back. Okay.
- 'Sir, please... our TRP...'
Ramanathan, everyone, including
you and I know that,
the video that has gone
viral on social media,
in the name of your
wife, Janaki, is fake.
She is a Srikankan lady.
Do you still need a Cyber- forensic,
report when things
are crystal clear?
We need it, sir.
Then, give me a request in writing.
- Here it is.
We will forward this to
Thiruvananthapuram.
They will send us
a report on this.
We can file a writ in
the court after,
receiving the Cyber-forensic report.
Prathapan sir,
if it reaches the court, the media
will have a field day.
Do we have to go for it?
Isn't it risky?
Let's see.
Don't worry. You may go.
I'll call you.
Don't panic.
- Okay.
Come.
Sir, I was asked to come here.
Is this what you're up to
right in the morning, huh?
Sir, please don't make an issue.
You needn't utter a word.
Yesterday, the girl and her mom
were yelling over this.
I won't repeat it, sir.
- Take out your mobile phone.
Sir, it was a mistake. - This is not
how you make a mistake.
Show me your mobile.
Give it to me.
Sir, my phone...
- Go and stand there.
His love and black mailing.
- Sir, I have deleted everything.
Get the printout
of the case report, quick.
Oh, Ravi, were you on leave?
No, I wasn't... I had
gone out to nab,
the accused in Mulanthuruthy
ATM fraud case,
along with the cops at
Thripunithara station.
Could you catch them?
- Just that our money went waste.
It happens.
- No use talking about it.
Sir, what's wrong?
- I lost my ATM card.
You should never write
the PIN on ATM cards.
I didn't know that. - Sir, please
call the bank and block her card.
Aneesh sir, our internet is down.
I'm using my own personal
data card to access the internet.
Cyber Cell, it seems.
Where is Baiju sir?
- He is in Prathapan sir's cabin.
Sanjay, isn't it ready? Didn't you
keep a copy of the Chennai police's FIR?
Is it not aligned?
- Yes, it is.
Where is Joy sir?
- He's over there.
Joy sir,
Please sign it.
That producer has gone mad.
For leaking someone else' cinema,
it's us who must go behind it.
I don't know how to write, dear.
Aunt, it's your money. Don't write
the PIN on your card, okay?
Okay, son. - Sir, please come
over after this is done.
Who asked you to come here?
- Anwar.
What's going on here?
- Your tea is kept there.
Which Anwar?
- Anwar Rasheed.
The producer of the
movie, Premam.
Look, this case has already
been closed.
There's nothing we can
do about it.
This is a closed file.
You may go.
Sir, can we meet the SHO?
- There's no use meeting him.
Go and mind your own business.
Who the nuts are they?
We will do one thing.
You should never write your PIN
number on your ATM card.
Where is the card that you
took last week?
Let me look!
- Joy, sir.
You remember, the 'Premam'
piracy case?
Yes.
It seems, our findings on
the case wasn't correct.
Who said it?
Those guys standing over there.
What did you say your name is?
- Antony.
And you?
- Vinay Dasan.
Vinay Das...
What do you do, Vinay Das?
Are you jobless?
I'm employed.
I work as a courier boy.
Blue Cart in Kochi.
What about you?
- I'm preparing for bank exams.
Meanwhile, I work part-time
in 'chicking'.
B-tech graduate, huh?
Yes, Computer Science.
So, what these B-tech graduates
are saying, is that,
our findings in Premam Piracy
case is wrong.
Sorry sir, that's not it.
Then, what else, sir?
Well, they are youngsters.
They might want to act in films.
If they can make friends
with Anwar Rasheed in this name,
they may get a minor
role in his next film.
What else?
Anyway, isn't this case about
that woman?
Yes.
- Let me see what she is saying.
Simply, to create a controversy,
what else?
There's no controversy behind this.
And you needn't try to
make one out of this.
On 29th of May.
On the first day of release
of Premam, at 2.10 pm,
someone uploaded the print on
the website of Tamil Rockers.
That's the main course of spread.
The police had seized the prints
from the CD outlets in Chennai,
on the very day itself.
They have also tracked the agents
who supply the prints to them.
I don't know, sir.
I swear, I don't know anything
about it.
Through them, we have also arrested
an admin of Tamil Rockers.
Sir, let us go. We don't
know anything.
After cross-questioning them,
we understood that,
It was a guy in New Zealand,
who uploaded it on
the Tamil Rockers website.
It's not legally possible either to
catch the guy in New Zealand,
or to question him.
Because piracy is not a
crime in New Zealand.
Sir, the print was not uploaded
on the Tamil Rockers website, first.
Then?
Just a day before, the print
was available on U torrent.
The file that appeared
in Tamil Rockers,
was initially downloaded
from there earlier.
Because both the copies contained
the water mark from Censor Board.
Sir, we had this project
while doing B-tech.
It is called Metadata analysing.
By using it,
we can get the details of each,
and every file uploaded
on the internet.
Details like the time the file has
been uploaded, its size, and so on.
So?
Sir, there were
six files altogether.
Its size was 960 Mb.
The total time taken to
upload the file of size,
960 Mb on internet is
one hour fifty minutes.
Okay.
- Which means 110 minutes.
I.e., in one minute, 8.72 Mb
of data is being transferred.
So, it's just 0.14 Mb in one second.
Sir, this 0.14 mbps is the average
net speed of BSNL network,
in a rural area inside Kerala.
So, most probably,
the file must have been uploaded
in Kerala.
Basheer.
- Yes, sir.
Ask Joshy sir, to come over.
Sir, the file please.
Lissy, I'm in an urgent meeting.
I'll call you back.
Sir,
This is what we were talking about.
- Sir, please check it.
On 28th of May, at 11.25pm,
i.e. the day before 'Premam'
was released...
The censor copy of this movie
was uploaded on U torrent.
Well, we can find out the IP address
based on the uploaded content.
And we can check if their
findings are genuine.
That is the protocol.
Well, sir, I'm not sure if U Torrent
would provide the IP address.
Well, we can request
them for the IP address,
via government authorities
sighting the case requirements.
Am I right?
It will take time, Peter.
But sir, even if we find out...
If they have uploaded
it using a proxy server,
the IP address that
we might get,
would be from... Say
Africa or Nigeria.
Sir, they have uploaded it under
the name, 'Hero'.
When we searched for it,
the profile picture used
was that of a dog.
There are seven files in the
uploaded folder.
Six of them are the mp4 files
of the film, Premam.
And one is a word file.
Isn't it a blank file?
What are we going to do with this?
Sir, when you create a word file,
the user name of
the corresponding system will,
appear in the property list
of the word file as author name.
Sir, if so,
it is the owner of the system who
has uploaded the files on the internet.
Baburaj.
A guy named Baburaj is
surely related to this case.
Either the word file was
uploaded by mistake,
while dragging the others,
or it was done on purpose
by someone.
But we need to find this Baburaj,
to get a clearer
picture of the case.
Then, why don't we line-up everyone
named Baburaj in Kerala,
and question them?
Dear sir, where on earth
are we going to find him?
Well sir, first,
we have to find out if Baburaj is,
anyone inside the
crew list of Premam.
So, we must cross-question
all the technicians in the film,
including the director.
Premam Piracy Case interrogations
at a turning point.
Hello.
Sir, just ten minutes.
I'm taking the list.
Please check the crew list.
Sir, there's a mail from
Vismaya studio.
Yes, I'm checking it.
There's no technician named
Baburaj in Vismaya studio.
Sir, this is the list
of Censor board employees,
who handled the film, 'Premam'.
'Film censoring has been stalled...'
- No one called Baburaj is here.
'...until Monday
as a protest against,'
'unnecessarily dragging censor board
Employees,' - Who is Baburaj?
'in the Premam Piracy Case.'
- Sir, the Film Chamber office?
Upstairs!
Are you here?
- I'm here, here...
This is a directory I collected
from the Film Chamber.
It contains the numbers of all the
technicians in the industry.
Okay, check it.
Sir, it was me who took the hard
disc to Vismaya for dubbing.
Hello, Baburaj.
- 'Hello.'
I'm Salam, art technician.
'Which Salam?'
- Where are you?
I'm in between a shooting.
- 'Which movie?'
'Why do you want to know?
Who are you?'
Salam! Salam!
- 'Which Salam?'
'Check for the correct number
before calling, you dumbo.'
I have been assisting Anwar for
the past two years.
Both Anand and Alphones
use to come to Di suit.
By 12.30 pm, noon,
the Cyber cops reached the
Alphones Puthran's flat in Aluva.
We were sure the movie
would go well in the theatres.
But we never expected such
a blow in between.
A lot of people within our industry
don't want our film do well.
Its common in the film industry.
Buddy,
if there's anything true about
what online media has been saying,
Thiruvananthapuram lobby has
a role in this piracy case,
so that the film doesn't
enter into the five hundred million club.
Do we have to think along that line?
- Why not?
If it is so,
we need to take the details of
seven people named Baburaj,
who have a connection with the
Thiruvananthapuram lobby.
Out of seven guys named Baburaj,
only three of them are active
in the industry right now.
I have taken the call list
of all the three.
One among them called
Priyadarsan several times,
on May 26th, 27th and 28th.
Sir.
- One Mr Baburaj Kalliath.
He's a native of Thiruvananthapuram.
He has received one and a half lakh
rupees via bank transfer from,
Priyadarshan's production house.
That too on May 29th, the very
day, Premam was released.
Will we go behind bars for this?
- Why are you standing here?
Joy sir asked us to wait here.
Do you know the IME number?
It's from Priyadarshan's studio,
the final copy has
gone for censoring.
Moreover, there is a rumour
among the fans,
that there are some guys
playing in the film industry,
not to break the 500 million
record of the film, Drishyam,
When all of these
are put together,
the game is clear. Isn't it, sir?
But how do we go about it without
informing the top authorities?
It will take a hell of a time if we
inform the authorities.
Sir, this is an opportunity.
Get into the car!
Aneesh, did you call anyone
over there?
I have spoken to Anoop
from Thiruvananthapuram wing.
What did Anoop say?
- His number is still active.
At times it says, switched off,
might be network issues.
Sir, he's in
Thiruvananthapuram for sure.
We are from the Cyber Cell.
Baburaj Sir,
we have been trying to get you
on call right from the morning.
It's either out of range
or switched off.
There's enough range. It
shows all the signal bars.
You got a password?
Tell me your password.
1,2...
3,4,5,6.
Listen,
you should collect all the available
data base from the cabins here.
Why do you want to search my stuff?
- He will tell you.
We are here to know
two things in particular.
Oh, really?
Firstly, on 26, 27, 28th of May…
To be accurate, three days
before Premam was released.
You have been talking to director
Priyadarshan on the phone.
What were you guys discussing?
Secondly, on 29th May,
One and a half lakh of rupees,
have been credited to your bank
account from Priyadarshan.
What's it for?
Wasn't I Priyan sir's assistant
for long?
Awesome! Are you asking us?
Yes, I am.
I have been with him since the film,
'Thenmaavinkombathu.'
So, sir...he's the guy
we are looking for.
Is there any problem with
Thenmaavinkombathu?
Chaps like you always do cheesy
stuff to trouble top authorities.
What's this all about, sir?
- It's just what you see.
Don't they have soft copies
of the same?
Sorry! I don't...
- Where's the bank statement?
Not this, back, back...
Just open the folder.
So, you have pretty good
dealings with Priyadarsan.
Obviously, he taught me cinema.
We talk very often.
When he comes to Thiruvananthapuram,
I meet him at hotel Pankaj.
What about the 1.5 lakhs
credited to your account?
Sir, you know it, Priyan sir
does a lot of Ads.
At times, he gives me Ads
to help my both ends meet.
I got the one and a half lakh as
an advance for an Ad.
I have proof.
Sir, please check them.
Geez! A lot of proofs, huh?
Let me see.
This is not data
but devotional songs,
of mother Goddess'.
Let me check it, sir.
Here's your phone.
Is it your own building?
Yes, I got it as dowry.
Dowry, huh?
- Nope, no dowry.
I meant to say her share
of her father's property.
This is not going to end
anywhere here, okay?
Sir, we got it wrong.
How ridiculous!
From now on, I'm not doing
this anymore.
Just to spoil the name
of our department.
Thiruvananthapuram lobby,
Cochin lobby... his mom's...
Leave it, Basheer.
Sir, we needn't blindly
trust Baburaj.
Let's keep an eye on him
for a couple of days.
Sure, we will get something.
Dear Aneesh, what's there
to monitor him so much?
We have searched his office,
say every nook and corner.
Also, cross checked
every single file.
Can't you understand from
his face that he's a coward?
I was just saying, sir.
Moreover...
Is Kerala Police a puppet
in the hands of random guys?
Everything has a protocol.
- Sir, this is...
You bloody...
You mustn't say anything
that you don't know.
In Kerala, we (Police) spend our
own money for such missions.
We haven't yet got reimbursement
for the earlier missions, either.
In between all this, you're
here with your antics.
Sir, we just said we were
suspicious of him.
Sorry, sir.
Hey kiddo, don't try
to justify yourself.
Come on, leave it.
This is quite common in
a case investigation.
We will find other ways.
My dear, sir, please keep
your mouth shut.
Crap!
Sir, we shall get down here.
Hey, come on, are you going
because you felt bad?
No, not at all.
- Then what?
You're going to Kochi, right?
Get in.
Hey, get in, Dasan.
We have some other
plans, that's why...
What plans? This is a lame
excuse. Just get in, guys.
That's not it, sir. Let's go.
We will call you.
Sorry sir.
Bye.
How will you go?
- We will go by bus.
Hey.
- Yes.
Where's the balance money?
What balance?
- Balance money of tea.
Oh, my goodness!!
I swear I forgot about it.
Okay.
What's wrong with you, Basheer?
They are kids, aren't they?
Chill, sir.
We should never over
entertain such guys.
'The Cyber Cell is baffled,'
'as they haven't got any clue
regarding the origin of censor copy,'
'from the raid conducted at
offices of various film people.'
I am fed up, man.
I quit.
How long have we
been after this?
Nothing's going to work out.
Just to have them
swear at us.
Close it, and keep it
somewhere far.
Engineer sir, do one thing.
Have a bath every morning,
wear your Blue Cart's uniform
and start begging.
What else should we do?
Is anyone giving us
a full time job?
But, is it possible to survive with
part-time jobs?
How long since we have
passed engineering?
Do we have a good job?
See this, it's her message.
She's asking me to go
and speak to her dad.
What should I tell him?
Give it to me.
We should prove something.
Not to others, but for
our sake, at least.
We must find him.
Don't try to make me
feel worthless, okay?
What you need is Baburaj, right?
Wait and watch.
We should have looked for Baburaj
on Facebook earlier itself.
Let me check how many people
named Baburaj are there on this.
We will list it out and find him.
List out how many of them
are related to cinema.
No one is going to hide anywhere.
Hey, just scroll back.
This one?
- Yes.
Isn't it that dog?
Yes, it is.
Show me the photo.
See this.
Isn't it the same dog?
Yes, both the dogs look alike.
It was copied from this.
See which place he belongs to?
- This is not a fake account.
This is an original account.
He's a KSRTC driver in Kazarkode.
Come on.
Buddy, you inform Joice sir, about it.
Shut your mouth, and
come on fast.
Anyway, I won't be able
to go home today.
Mom, I'm taking this Chit money
for the time being. - Antony.
Hey, give it back.
- I'll give it to you next week.
No, I must pay it urgently.
- Mom, pay you next week.
What will I say when they
come to collect the money?
He finds penny lying
outside, and he takes it!
Enough! I'm keeping it back.
I have put five hundred back; I'll pay
the balance next week.
Have food and go.
- No, I'll eat later.
Eat and go, I say.
Where are you both going
at midnight?
We have work. - If it is for
cigarettes, I'll burn you alive.
Are you wearing my slippers?
- I'm to blame for cooking them food.
Man, does your mom light
cigarettes on a burner?
Eat and go, I say.
- We will eat after coming back.
Get lost.
Come on, dude!
I'm asking you,
where are you going?
Tell her, dear. - Dasan, tell me
We're going nearby...
just till Kazakode.
Kazarkode, huh?
KAZARKODE - 83 kms.
'The bus departing this morning
from Kazarkode...'
Sister, is there anyone named
Baburaj here?
Yes, he is a driver.
Driver...? Where is he right now?
He's gone to Neeleshwaram for duty.
He'll be back by 8.30.
Is he Baburaj Thomas?
Yes, the one with a long beard.
- Yes, yes, thanks, sister.
He works here.
There's a Neeleshwaram bus,
reaching here at 8.30.
He is the driver of the bus.
Please give me a bottle of water.
'The bus from Kazarkode to
Mangalore will depart shortly.'
A bus to Uppalam
has been parked in,
the southern side of
the bus station.'
Sir, has the bus to
Bandadka come?
8.15.
- Okay.
Hey! Antony.
Hi, Satheesh.
- Hi, Babu.
The tyres have worn out.
Change it.
Buy booze in the evening.
You must buy it, idiot.
- Evening...for sure.
Come on, quick.
Where is he?
You go to the other side.
Dasan.
Come here.
What is it?
Here, here, here...
He is inside.
Inside this room?
Who are you?
Are you not Baburaj?
What do you want?
Brother, we have been searching for you.
We have got all the details
of your Facebook account.
What nonsense are you saying?
Brother, just take a look at it.
Isn't it your Facebook profile?
- Which one?
My dear friend, see this.
I know only this.
I don't even have Facebook with me.
Then, how will you collect details,
of my Facebook which
doesn't even exist?
If so, who uploaded the
print of Premam?
This will become a police
case, tell us the truth.
Don't give me a headache, buddy.
Don't go, tell us the truth.
- There's no need to argue.
Tomorrow, the police will come and
you will have to answer them.
Police?
- Yes, why not?
It's a piracy case.
You will go behind bars.
Piracy, huh?
If you're this adamant,
the police will come, and this
will go out of your hands.
You photo will come in the
newspapers. - Get lost.
Yes, you will lose your
job right away.
Just get lost, you... I'm not
the type you think I am.
Brother, brother, brother...
See this.
Is it not your dog?
This one?
He is our Tomy.
I have a sister in Varkala.
It is her dog.
Tomy.
Her name is Sisily.
She is a PWD clerk.
My brother-in-law was in the Gulf.
Now, he is here.
Pious.
We are not on good terms.
Property issues.
They have a son.
He's a brat studying
in Varkala, VHSC.
Jerry.
- What is it, sir?
What's the problem?
Is there anything wrong?
- Why do you want to call him?
What's the matter, sir.
- Hey, come here.
Come.
- What is it, son?
Don't stare like an
ostrich, come here, kid.
What is the issue, sir?
Come on.
Come on, kid.
- You had us eat our brains out.
Sit here.
What's it, sir?
What's the problem?
Is there anything wrong?
Of course, that's why we are
here at this late hour.
Isn't it, kid?
Do you want to speak,
or shall I go?
Well, don't you know your son has
started a new business?
He is earning a lot,
by uploading new films
on the internet.
Isn't it?
Where is your laptop, kiddo?
Sir, that must be there
in his room.
I'll go take it.
What is the password?
It is 'motherf**ker1...
What is it?
'motherf**ker123'
Mother...
Did you create a Facebook
account in your uncle's name?
Tell me.
Do you know about the illegal
things your son is doing,
by creating a fake ID in the
name of your brother?
Why is Jerry angry
with your uncle?
My parents don't like him.
Mom has asked me not
to speak with him.
Didn't you hear what
your son just said?
Basheer, what's with it?
Sir, I can't find anything.
Where is the print?
It is there in the hidden files.
Sir, shall I...?
Let me do it.
- Basheer, let him give it a try.
Then, you try, kiddo.
I have already searched all of them.
All are learning material, huh?
You love biology, don't you?
You are smart.
Sir, all the files are in here.
'Stop chatting! Just go!'
Wherefrom did you get the print?
Come on, open your
mouth and tell us.
Don't hurt him, sir.
Tell me, son.
Keep it.
- Sir,
See, we are taking him along.
Joy, come to Varkala station
tomorrow, early morning.
We will get him to confess
before that.
He would have done
it by mistake.
Please don't take him now.
He is a kid.
Tell us, what's the problem?
- Don't take him now, please, sir.
Sir, I'll bring
him tomorrow morning.
He is a kid; he must have...
- Joy, move out of our way.
Move.
- Sir, he is a school-going kid.
Please sir, please don't
take him now.
Sir, I'll do as you say.
You come along with me.
Don't be scared.
Don't hurt him, sir.
If you co-operate with us,
you will have no problem at all.
Why are you complicating
things?
Aren't you a kid?
Do you know what will happen
if you go to jail at your age?
Your life will be spoiled.
Do you know why we came
at night?
To solve the issue without the
media and the public knowing.
If you are this adamant,
how is it possible?
That will not work.
Tell me the truth.
We will take care of you.
You will have no problem at all.
You just tell us who
gave it to you.
Son, tell me.
Don't get tense.
Tell me the truth.
Who gave it to you?
Anjali gave it to me.
Which Anjali?
She is my classmate.
I got it from her.
But how? Tell me.
We have been in love since 8th grade.
Eh? Since what grade?
Sir, eighth grade.
She had a few photos of
our tenth class reunion.
I took the pen drive from her
to copy those pictures.
I found the print of Premam
inside a folder.
How did the print get
into the pen drive?
I asked her once that,
how did she get the print of
an unreleased movie?
She said she would tell me later,
and asked me not to tell anyone.
Sir, she is a nice girl.
Do you have the print of
Premam with you?
I know you have it
in the pen drive.
I'm here at the back seat.
We are police.
Vishnu is under our custody.
We know that you leaked
the print of Premam.
Anjali C.
How did the video get into the pen
drive that you gave to Jerry?
I don't know anything, sir.
We have not yet informed
either your parents or the school.
We didn't even bring
a lady cop just because,
we didn't want to
make trouble for you.
I don't know anything.
- Tell me, girl,
wherefrom did you get it?
If not, this vehicle
will go straight,
to Kallambalam police station.
This is not the way the
police would question there.
Sir, please don't say like that.
She might have done
it unwittingly.
She's a good girl.
Please don't cry, Anjali.
Stop crying, first.
Anjali, speak out.
My lover gave it to me.
No, I'm not the one
who gave it to her.
She gave it to me.
Tell us, kiddie.
Is he the one who gave it to you?
- Not him.
Then?
- Akhilesh.
What?
Akhilesh?
Who is Akhilesh?
He is a system operator
at the censor board.
Where is your Akhilesh right now?
He said he lives somewhere
near Poonthura colony.
I don't know anything else, sir.
'This is a case, and it has
its seriousness.'
'Police is no Childs play.
It needs a lot of effort.'
'It's about taking up
a lot of tension.'
'Why would I send a low quality
censor copy to someone,'
'from my system?'
'Am I crazy?'
Sir, this is the house.
Joy.
Are you not Akhilesh?
- Yes.
I'm Akhilesh.
- Who are you?
Us?
- Yes, who are you?
Your mom's husband.
It's a new film, so I just thought,
let her watch.
Just walk.
I'll lose my image, sir.
Everyone around is looking at me.
Now, everyone's going to know...
- What boorish hair?
Well...
When you save blue movies,
it's enough to create a folder inside
program files in C drive, right?
Yes.
Nobody will find out?
He loves porn.
We got him after taking
a lot of twists and turns.
Yes, we got him.
'We got Baburaj through the dog.'
'Jerry through Baburaj.'
'Anjali via. Jerry.'
'And through Anjali, her
lover Akhilesh.'
'Now, we can tell everyone,'
'that we also have a role
in solving a case,'
'that drove Kerala mad.'
'To be frank,
this is a hope for us.'
'The hope that we can achieve
many more things in life.'
He admitted to have committed
the crime.
We will manage the rest
of the things officially.
That is the protocol.
Move.
Sir, why didn't you take them?
Aren't they one among us?
'We always have this fate.'
'We joined for engineering at Selam,'
'as we took pride in getting
good grades in plus two.'
'Since then, we have been trying
ways to come up in life.'
'We managed to pass
around 46 papers,'
'with the help of bits and
writing gas.'
'But life isn't like that.'
'My name's Antony George.'
My name is Vinay Dasan.
I'm twenty-five years old.
I had...
I have... Mother.
My father's name is George.
And he is no more.
My positives are my friendly nature,
that brings a smile on the face.
My negative is working too hard.
I think we lost it due to
lack of fluency in English.
It would never come
out when needed.
Give it.
We should have studied CBSE.
Man, what do you say about going
for bank coaching in Kollam?
Is it costly?
Did you study engineering
to work in a bank?
I am fed up of this engineering
and stuff.
'Our neighbours and relatives,'
'belong to a special
category of psychos,'
'who find fault in
everything they see.'
'As we are not in a position to
pay back our loan money,'
'we are forced, not to pick
some phone calls in life.'
'I don't care about what everyone
says about me.'
'But I'm answerable
to only one person.'
Listen to me.
- What?
Who are you showing
Your stubbornness to?
I'll call you back.
Hello...
- Listen, girl.
To have good things in life,
you will have to ignore some...
That's the fate of every
single girl.
'She has been with me since
my higher secondary.'
'Though she always fights with me,
she loves me a lot.'
'I need to find a job,'
'before meeting her dad to
ask her hand in marriage.'
'Whenever my attempts for
a job fail, I think,'
'God will have better plans for me.'
'No chance.'
'Great philosophy, low life.'
Just pick the call, hello.
Hey, sir is here.
Hang up, hang up.
Want a smoke?
No, sir... We don't smoke.
That's good.
The final credit goes to the Cyber Cell.
But... The actual
credit goes to you.
We don't need any credit, sir.
We did it for some money.
Aren't you happy?
- Yes, thank you, sir.
Sir,
Please don't mistake
us for asking this.
Do you want money?
- No, we don't want any money.
Then what?
Do you have any job
openings there?
Where?
In the Cyber Cell.
That's difficult, dear.
You need to pass the PSC test,
and undergo police training...
Also, the Cyber Cell recruits
candidates with computer knowledge.
You try for PSC.
No! PSC and all won't work out.
Just give it a try.
- Be positive.
We are writing the tests.
Sir, just a minute.
To be frank,
after plus two, we joined B-tech like
jumping onto the bandwagon.
We are not getting a job.
So, life is being creepy.
Who all are there
at your house?
At home, I have my dad, mom...
A sister...
No, I had a sister; she
expired four years ago.
'Why are you finding it
difficult to face me?'
'I want to know.'
Dear, I'll come and meet you.
We will discuss it then.
'I adjusted my shift only because
you said you would meet me today.'
Dear, I told, I would come.
Please wait for me, please.
- 'I'm still waiting.'
'But for how long?'
Please don't repeat the same thing.
Didn't I tell you I would come?
Sir, shall we leave?
You are leaving?
- Okay, All the best.
Call sometimes, or else we
might forget. Isn't it, Joy?
Bye.
- See you, sir.
Okay.
What is it?
- Come.
What is the matter?
- Nothing.
They are good, aren't they?
- They rock.
They will sail through.
What makes a jobless
chap like you so busy?
At least my tensions...
My problems...
Can't you understand all those?
Okay, tell me, what's your worry?
You! You are my tension.
Didn't I tell you earlier?
I got a job.
The offer letter has come.
Supernova, it's a government
hospital in Ireland.
The salary is two lakhs per month.
I would like to go.
What is your opinion?
What are you supposed to do if
you have received the offer letter?
You must go.
- So?
You go and settle down there…
And then take me along.
Wonderful!
Antony, you either find a job,
and talk to my mom or...
I don't want to introduce you as a
husband who is dependent on me.
Be practical.
You can go on advising me
to be practical.
But I'm not getting a job.
But, you aren't even trying for it.
- Who told you that I'm not trying?
Antony, don't try to blindly
justify yourself.
I'm not justifying or anything.
Who else should I talk to
about my grief?
I'm fed up.
I'm really fed up.
Can't you be a bit more sincere?
At least towards yourself?
Are you even half sincere to me
as you are to your friends?
Am I not tolerating you since
the twelfth grade?
You do want to break
up with me?
Go for it.
No need to create a dramatic scene.
When you heard about the
two lakhs salary from Ireland,
I became an utter waste for you.
You may go to Ireland, and enjoy.
Dude.
Are you still thinking about it?
Leave it, dear.
It's good she broke up now.
Whatever is over is gone!
Crap.
She's gone to Ireland, right?
Ireland is not a place that
we don't know.
Do you want to go
to Ireland now?
Ramanathan,
the report has come from
Thiruvananthapuram.
According to their report,
when they processed the
video for the details,
they confirmed that,
it is Janaki herself in the video.
How could it be her?
Are you saying the ones who
prepared the report are idiots?
It's not her, sir.
Hey…
You might say that it's not her.
But this is the proof.
Do you get it?
When you were high on drugs and
alcohol, she must have enjoyed too.
What will you do if such an ill-fate
comes upon your mom or sister?
What did you just say?
You moron, are you messing
with us at our fiefdom?
Sir, do you know how much
did we suffer due to this?
Leave me, sir.
I'll take his piss out.
I was a drunkard during
the time she decided to live with me.
I know everything about her.
Can't he show some courtesy?
Who are you to teach us (cops),
courtesy?
Please be seated, Ramanathan.
Sit, Ramana...
Get lost, you…
- Hey, Bash...
Sorry, Ramanathan.
Let's talk it out.
It's been 7-8 months since
the whole ordeal began.
That is a video made by
deceiving a naive girl,
at some other place.
It's my friend who
spread the news,
that Ramanathan's wife
is on a blue movie.
I told everyone a hundred
times that it's not her.
No one believed.
Everyone is more interested
in believing, it's my wife.
Our helplessness,
is what the world is celebrating
as 'Viral'... isn't it, sir?
You will be disgusted to hear the
comments passed by everyone,
including my daughter's male
teachers and schoolmates.
My child stopped going to school.
She is staying at my sister's house.
She's scared to come
home, it seems,
scared to live with her
own mother, hatred...
I know for sure that
it's not my wife.
It's for my daughter,
I'm here.
What should I do now?
Tell me, sir.
Do you want me to go
to Delhi or Bombay?
We also want to live here.
My daughter wants to live here.
When I see her face,
my entire day cripples.
That's not her in the video.
What are these people
preparing the reports doing there?
Sir.
Hi, what's up?
- We are good.
No calls, nothing... since then.
We were a bit busy.
The reason why we asked
you here is...
Last week, we had
a meeting with IG
Joy...
As a part of upgrading
the Cyber Cell,
they are planning to hire
technically qualified people,
as interns in Cyber Cell.
It's been two weeks since we
received the government order.
Who and how to hire people
is purely my discretion.
If you like, you can join us.
You can assist us in
our investigation.
But you will not get all the
benefits the police receive.
It's like a temporary posting.
But not entirely...
You will get a salary of around ten
thousand.
But you won't become permanent
by time as other jobs.
That's okay.
So, aren't you joining?
Yes, sir.
Okay, sir.
Okay, Sir.
- Come on.
Why think so much?
Just shave it.
Shave it, I say.
Shave underneath
your moustache.
And when you roll up
your moustache...
Only if I start from here,
I can end it here.
This is not police but the Cyber Cell.
A beard is fine.
- That's okay, you shave it off.
You will become clean.
- Tell me.
Has your son passed
his exams?
He has a good salary.
Seventy five thousand rupees.
'So much?'
- Mom, don't stretch it.
You get lost, boy.
They always poke me
about you being jobless.
Let her feel green with envy
for some time.
I need to call two more...
Did you get a job?
- Yes.
Where is it?
- Cyber Cell.
Is it permanent?
- No, it's a temporary job.
Oh, too bad.
Such a negative chap!
Hi, aunt!
All good?
All the best.
Thank you, sir.
Just meet Joy, sir.
Aren't you happy?
Tuck in shirt and all, huh?
- It's just here.
What uniform do you
have at the Cyber Cell?
Just this.
We are supposed to wear
a uniform on Mondays.
But no one wears.
Why I asked is I have set
of khaki pants for me.
Since this is our first day...
He is Sanjay.
- Yeah, we know.
Hi, sir.
This is our team.
- Hi.
Hi.
Basheer.
- Yes.
Our guys are joining today.
Hi, sir.
You may sit here.
You can keep this chair there.
This is your place.
- Thank you, sir.
Well, you probably
know them, right?
Yes, we talked last time.
She is Anita.
- Thank you, sir.
Das... Antony...
Sir, here are the details
of the admin.
Dasan.
- All the best.
All the best.
- Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
Hello, they just joined.
Just a minute.
So, all the best. Rock it.
- Thank you.
Basheer.
Just brief them...
About everything.
Yes, they are joining today.
I was arranging chairs for them.
- Happy, huh?
You are the first engineers
to make it to the Cyber Cell.
Passing B-tech is possible
only for people with brains.
But my boy passed
all the papers.
There are around forty six
papers in total.
He studied everything.
He is good at studies, isn't he?
- Yes, of course.
He is very talented.
He got a job too.
Where is he working?
- In the police...
Really?
He's in the Cyber Cell.
Name?
- Parveen, sir.
Parveen.
- Parveen.
Here... Where... Just ask him
where in Kerala is he staying?
Where in Kerala are you staying?
- Perumbaavoor, sir.
Where are you from?
Assam.
What's ... Er...
What...
Paisa...
What?
- What's your problem?
My six thousand rupees has been stolen.
Six thousand rupees!
He lost six thousand rupees, it seems.
Huh! I will definitely call...
Just a minute.
Please come here.
Who are you in here?
I.	I'm a staff in here.
You should solve my issue.
What's your problem, sir?
- Is this a cucumber town?
It's 60,000 rupees I lost
in the past 8 hours.
You must return
my money back.
Otherwise, you...
Just a minute.
- Are you going?
Joy sir,
Stop there, stop.
Let me talk.
What's your problem, sir?
Who are you?
- I'm the ASI here.
ASI's board is there, and
why don't you sit there?
Instead, why are you
hanging around here?
What's your problem, sir?
Sit. Sit. Please sit.
Why is this place like
a hen's pen?
Is this the Cyber Cell?
Yes, this itself is the Cyber Cell.
What's the case, sir?
When I was
driving my car,
a lady called on my phone.
She said the validity of my
card has expired,
and asked me to send the OTP
number to renew the card.
I sent her the OTP number
I lost thirty thousand rupees on the spot.
The next morning, another
thirty thousand were gone.
Sir, you need to be careful.
You shouldn't share the OTP
number with anyone.
I was cautious while
sending it to them.
It's my OTP number
I sent them.
I must get my money back.
- Antony...
Yes, you will get it, sir.
Aneesh, get the details from him.
- Okay, sir.
See from which number
he got the call... And trace it.
Sir, what's your name?
Your name?
My name is Balachandran.
Please write it down.
Where are you working, sir?
I'm the manager of SBY bank,
Kadavanthara.
What did you just say?
I'm the manager of SBY bank,
Kadavanthara.
Aneesh, please deal with it yourself.
I'm the manager. So, I should
get my money back.
You will get it, sir.
I will call you back.
Wow! Yummy!
The curry is yummy.
Super.
You started looking cool after
shaving your beard.
Mummy, even I have
shaved my beard.
Did you even have a beard?
Your dosa is not as tasty as before.
Sir,
I was in love with a girl.
I had sent her a few
photos and videos.
Now, she is using those photos
and videos,
to blackmail me.
Has she sent her photos to you?
No, she hasn't.
- No?
Where is she right now?
The girl is in Philippines.
Philippines, huh?
Why is she asking
money from you?
She's asking money because,
the photos I sent were
a bit cheesy.
What kind of photos?
The other kind of photos...
You mean, nude?
Yes, kind of...
To a Philippine girl?
Sir, it was by a mistake.
- Have you seen those photos?
No, I haven't seen them.
- Haven't you shown him those?
Why? Isn't he, your friend?
Why didn't you show it to him?
How can I show those
kind of photos to him?
Were you drunk then?
Yes, I was a little drunk.
Basheer sir, this is your case.
This is a case, he
shows interest in.
Oh, is she from Philippines?
How did you fall in love with her?
I sent her a request hoping
to learn English.
You know what,
even Philippinos don't know
English properly.
If you have such a wish,
you should be sending requests
to English girls in the US or UK.
Can you help, sir?
What is she saying now?
She is demanding one lakh.
- No, it is one and a half.
Is it one or one and half?
- Sir, it is one.
Are you going to pay
her the money?
Sir, I don't have any
money with me.
Okay, then tell me, what
shall we do now?
Sir, he's getting married
next week.
Marriage!
He's getting married, please
do something about it.
What's your name?
- Shibukuttan.
Well Shibukuttan, what we
can do about this is,
If at all she leaks your
photos or details,
on Instagram, Facebook or You-tube,
We can remove it from there.
Jeez!
There's no provision to stop
her from posting them.
Because, she's in Philippines.
Moreover, we don't have the capacity
to go there and interrogate her.
Sir, won't you help?
- Sure.
It's my marriage.
- Don't worry, we will solve it.
Mr Antony.
What's up?
Did you get any details
about that Ashwathi Achu?
It's hopeless, man.
Nothing yet? What's it showing?
- It's invalid.
Invalid?
- Yes, it's all fake.
Let me see for mutual friends.
Dude, just open the Facebook.
- That's mine.
Just show me.
Just a minute.
Why do you want to look
at my Facebook?
I'll give it back just now. - Don't
device any stratagem with it.
Unlike before, it's the Cyber Cell.
Go, man.
We will feel embarrassed.
So, this is the matter.
Didn't you leave her?
How many times did
I warn you?
Aren't you done getting
dumped by that girl once?
Do you know,
only those who were blocked,
by someone have succeeded in life.
Fresh proverb, huh?
Did you make it now?
Yes, it came from my heart.
Give it to me.
You will understand it only once some
one ditches you for the second time.
Pass me the cigarette.
- Don't finish it, okay?
Hey, buddy, the salary has
been credited.
Why are you early today?
Nothing.
What's this?
I bought it from my first salary.
Saree, huh?
If you don't like it, you
can get it exchanged.
It's a nice saree.
Dear sir,
I ordered an I-phone for
five thousand using a link on WhatsApp.
I-phone for just five thousand rupees?
- Yes.
Show me the phone.
It's a tile.
Wow! What a phone, man?
Sir, are you kidding me?
I raised the money, borrowing
and doing catering work.
Sir, will you get my money back
instead of taking photos?
Let's inquire about this.
We came to collect the details.
We will see to it.
It's enough I get my money back.
I leave the phone.
It seems like we forced him...
Aren't you sure if
I would get my money?
Didn't you hear, we are
here to collect the details.
What course are you doing?
- B-tech.
B-tech, believing to get an
I-phone for just five thousand rupees.
Keep it with you.
- Same pinch, okay?
Fix the tile using cement, okay?
I'm super pranked.
Ma'am, you cops are so
irresponsible.
I'm not able to chill out
peacefully.
Man, what a dark scene is this!
Hey, just remove your
cooling glass.
Is the dark scene over now?
- Yes.
Do you have your mobile with you?
Give it to her.
What is it, Basheer?
- Give it to her.
Sir, read this and see.
Sir, we had gone for a
trip to Goa last week.
When we were back home,
none of our costly
stuff were there.
Bog off, kiddo.
Madam, it's not here that
You complain about a case like this.
Instead, you must lodge
a complaint with the police.
It has no connection with us.
No sir, there's a small
connection with us.
When they started their tour,
this halfwit put a post
on Facebook.
See it.
- Sir, it's nothing.
I just wrote, five day trip to
Goa, rocking with mom.'
Isn't it, mom?
- Don't get beaten up by me.
Below the post,
there's a comment with
a photo of Kylo Ren.
'' Sweets, you rock it there,
and we will rock it here.''
Dear, sir, first of all,
He is not my friend.
They are thieves for sure.
Ma'am, you may register
a complaint with the police.
It's them who must
see to the case.
Only if they pass anything
to us, we take action on it.
Won't we get our things back, sir?
- You will. Better approach the police.
Boy, you come here.
My phone...
- You will get it, come with me now.
What is your name?
My name is Sanju Techie.
- Is Techie your initial?
No, sir, I put it for style.
Techie's mom, you have
only one like this at your house?
I have one more like him.
He's gone for a trip,
to Manali.
Kiddo, you must not share
such posts on Facebook.
Like... Time, or the number of
days you're going, etc...
Don't share it publicly.
You can share it with your friends
if they must know.
Do you get it?
You shouldn't do such
things from now.
Why are you making it
dark every time, huh?
Sir, please speed up things.
Mom, all is set.
After the police forward it to us,
we will take care of the rest.
Everything's okay.
- Thank you, sir.
Come, let's go.
- Mom, just pass me the phone.
Why? - I want to post a selfie
saying, 'Feeling frustrated'.
Selfie. Aren't you done with this?
You better take a selfie
with your mom's corpse.
What's wrong with taking a photo?
- Just walk.
Oh, I see...
When did they contact you
for the first time?
Isn't the question clear?
Since when did they start
calling you?
That's the question. Answer me.
Don't worry. Tell us.
Four days after receiving the mail,
a Tamil lady called me.
She told, she is a nurse working
in an hospital in Ireland.
Then...
She confirmed that I have been
appointed to a hospital,
under Ireland government
with immediate effect.
Also, I'll get a
salary of two lakhs...
So? - How much did
you pay them initially?
Ma'am, as form fee,
they asked me to pay
fifteen hundred to an account.
Do you have the account
details with you?
Account details...
Sir, here are the details.
Antony.
- Sir.
Just see if you can track
the account number,
and the mobile number.
Go.
- Okay, sir.
Did you give any amount thereafter?
Hello.
Alphonsa...
Hey, girl.
I'm asking, how much
did you give in total?
Well...
Sir, we have given them
two lakh seventy-five thousand rupees.
Geez! Giving this much money
to a stranger...?
In what age are you
people living, brother?
My dear girl, don't you
have any friends,
who you can ask for a second
opinion on things like this?
I don't know.
- Tell you one thing,
don't go after her again,
even if she tries to woo you.
I'm saying this because,
I know you very well.
Is anything getting on to your head?
- Yes, it is.
And something serious...
Unlike before, you have
a job now.
So, behave accordingly.
Don't even mind her by any
chance, heard it?
Excuse me.
- Yes.
Those who advised me
earlier just pulled out.
Please help me.
I guess you were a person
who took sensible decisions?
My bad.
I trusted them a lot.
That's how they convinced me.
They were okay with my IELTS score
and my experience here.
Firstly, they called for
an interview,
with the hospital recruitment board.
Later, they cancelled it
and rescheduled it on Skype.
So, through Skype,
I had a short chat with a person
abroad for four to five minutes.
Later, in the name of medical test,
exam fee etc.,
they had me pay seventy thousand rupees.
I even got an offer letter
after four days.
Then came... Visa charges...
Ireland intelligence clearance...
I gave them
two lakhs for all this.
But, they asked me
for only half the amount,
a nurse would normally
pay for going abroad.
That's the part that
attracted me.
I don't know what to do next.
I was devastated on seeing
my daughter,
sweat blood for a poor salary
in a private hospital.
That's why I...
We don't have anything
other than this.
Haven't you left yet?
What is it?
I was explaining the problem
to sir.
Sir? You mean, him?
He is just an apprentice, trainee.
Ah, you do one thing,
you leave now.
We will see to it, and
call you back.
Girl, you cheer up and go now.
Such greedy fellows!
How foolish are they!
Sir, this job a luxury?
Isn't it?
Can't they live moderately with
whatever job they have here?
Is Ireland or Canada the only
option to make money?
But, don't they need salary?
Son, the salary is not
just two or three lakhs...
But five or ten thousand is
also a salary.
Do you understand?
Greedy chaps!
Hello.
You go get me a tea.
Guys, Prathapan sir, is asking
for you both, go.
Hey, is the girl your friend?
What, sir?
I mean, the nurse...is
she, your friend?
She was my junior in twelfth grade.
Dear Prathapan sir, her complaint
regarding the job fraud case, correct?
She ditched him when
she got that job.
To be frank, it was
a great ditch.
No sir, she didn't ditch
me or anything.
That's because of her situation.
Son, that phenomenon
is still known as 'ditching'.
Do one thing.
You investigate that case.
Sir...
How I wish that my ex-lovers
who ditched me in life,
come and stand in front
of me like this!
But it never happened.
This is an opportunity.
You lead this case.
Isn't it the 'heroism'?
Do it, man.
Isn't it, your first independent
case investigation?
Take it up with courage.
We are here to support you.
'More than sixty per cent private
hospitals in Kerala,'
'are deceiving nurses without
giving them,'
'the minimum wage of 12,000
as against government order.'
'Due to low salaries,'
'many are struggling to pay
back their educational loans.'
Man, see if there's
any case based in Kochi.
Sir, it's a lady called Nirmala from
Chennai, who called me first.
She said, she wanted to conduct
a nursing recruitment drive,
to a hospital in the Netherlands.
They have come to Kochi
for about 3-4 times.
Her husband was one...
Collin Peter is a
Dutch citizen.
I was convinced when she said,
her husband would help out
with things in Netherland.
Do you have the photos of the
foreigner and the Tamil lady?
Yes, sir.
- Let me see.
Sir, these are the guys.
They are the ones
who f***ed my life.
No, he is not the one.
He has long hair.
He is fat too.
I want to see the mail
you received.
The mails they received
are from an e-mail ID whose domain,
is similar to that of Supernova
hospital, i.e. hr@supernova.
It takes three to four thousand
rupees to create such a domain.
Sir, we know it ourselves,
we get a lot of such mails
on our Gmail.
We need to know if any similar mode
of operations has taken place,
in any of the cities in Kerala.
Chances are very high.
'My name is Krishnaveni,
from Nagarcoil.'
'I don't know what I must
do right now,'
'that is why I'm making this video.'
'I think someone cheated me.'
Do you see any similarity
between Alphonsa issue and this?
There are a lot of
similarities between
the calls received by both
Alphonsa and Krishnaveni.
'They took two lakhs from me.'
- We got the details from her.
First, a call from a Tamil lady,
then a foreigner.
Their mode of operation, mailer,
server... Everything is similar.
Normally, online fraudsters
follow this pattern of,
stealing a few thousands.
But now, they have lost lakhs...
This has happened
for the first time.
Sir, as soon as the money comes
in to the fraudster's account,
they transfer it to various
accounts in Qatar and Oman.
All the account holders are based
in Tamilnadu and Karnataka.
But we are unable to track them.
Sir, I got this from
Google last day.
In a place called Jamtara,
a bunch of people had indulged
in an online fraud case.
They collect the resumes and
bio data of people,
from job websites like
Naukri and Indeed.
Then, they call the candidates,
offer them engineering jobs,
collect fifteen hundred rupees from each,
and then, no response...
Senior officials investigated
the Jamtara case.
They even found out, who
did it, and from where...
But no one could ever go
there, and arrest them.
Well, sir, I don't think this case
is related to the Jamtara case.
If at all they were related,
the language they used in
the call would have been,
either Hindi or Gujarati,
or local English.
But in this case, it is Tamil.
Since all these accounts are
based in Tamilnadu,
this is a South Indian
racket, sir.
There are going to be more victims.
That's sure, sir.
Many of them wouldn't have realized
that they were cheated.
Others wouldn't say it openly
due to embarrassment.
There're going to be more
names in the coming days.
A common link!
That's what is missing here.
Dasan.
- Yes.
Hey, just show me the video
Prathapan sir just showed us.
Is this the one?
Hey, isn't it Krishnaveni?
Yes, it's true.
Madam, do you hear me?
- 'Sir, I don't. Network...'
Have you come to Kochi in April?
On twelfth April?
- 'Yes, sir.'
'I had an interview
there in Medicity.'
All of these nine people,
had been in Kochi some day
in between April 15-30th,
for various purposes.
But all of them had checked-in
to the Pluto mall.
'Yes, yes, I had gone to
the Pluto mall.'
Sir, this is a lucky contest.
If you fill in your name
and address...
You might win it.
- Thanks.
Pen?
- No, I'll do it later.
What's it?
- Dasan. I'm down.
I'll come, be there.
What's the matter?
See this, this is a contest
conducted in here.
It contains all the details of
a person like the name,
address, mobile number,
e-mail id and occupation.
So what?
Aren't these details more than
enough to easily trick someone?
What you are saying? That this is
connected to the job fraud case?
Why not? It contains A to Z
about a person.
That's in last April, dear.
You come, let's ask about it.
If you have an alternate number,
write that too.
Brother.
- Hi, sir.
Will it win?
- Of course, if your time is good.
No way, I didn't win anything
for the Vishu contest last time.
Sir, how many contests have
passed after April?
You will win this for sure.
Pal, you call Krishnaveni,
and ask her if she had filled any
coupon when she visited Pluto mall.
Hello.
- Sir.
Dear, when you came to Pluto mall,
did you fill any coupon for
a contest or something?
Yes, I had filled one for my sister.
Later, I filled one for
myself, and put it inside.
Oh, really?
Brother, brother...
Who's coordinating the contest?
The mall itself.
Why do you ask?
No, it's nothing...
We are the marketing staff of
Q-tec educational centre.
Is it possible to get the details of
the coupons filled by the visitors?
No, no, no, no...
If we can get the details of people
between the age of 15-20,
that will be very useful
for our marketing.
We are conducting this contest
only to give gifts to people.
And not for selling data.
Why are you manipulating things?
Sir, we can make a payment...
Can't you understand, what
I just said? Please go.
Sir, we ask you because
it's for our job...
Didn't I tell you once?
Go, man.
Get lost.
They are moving these
coupons somewhere.
That's for sure.
What are you saying?
I don't think so.
If so, we will do one thing.
We will inform our office about it.
Let them do the needful.
If we call them before confirming
it, Basheer sir will be little us.
What can we do now?
Were you the guy who came to
that office with the coupons?
What is it, sir?
Who are you giving
these coupons to?
I swear I don't know.
- Bloody...
Tell me the truth.
We are from the Cyber Cell.
There's a complaint against you.
We will put you in jail.
I swear I don't know.
Every Friday, a van comes here.
I know only that.
- What time on Friday?
Why are you here?
Have you worn a hat and all?
Make it a full cup. Come on...
Take it.
Oh, sorry,
I don't drink milk tea.
Couldn't you say so before?
- I drink black tea.
Brother, order cancelled.
Black tea will make you even darker.
Sanu, where were you after coming
back from Selam? Long time...
My family forced me to
do M-Tech after B-Tech.
And did you take it up?
For that,
I need to pass B-tech, right?
Yes, you should pass B-tech.
What about you?
Did you find any job?
After B-tech,
we are looking over...
So, still jobless!
What about you?
Did you find a job?
Yeah, we are on it,
investigating things.
Can't you try some simple stuff?
Like civil service or something.
How ridiculous!
Yes, we are trying for it.
What I want to ask you is...
This data entry thing, right?
Is it a good business?
I'm doing it as a part
time job, right?
I get two to three hundred per day.
If it is full-time, you will get
five to six. Do you want to give it a try?
That's not the plan...
The thing is, his uncle told us that
he can loan us some money.
If we start a business of your
kind, will it work out?
How does it run?
Can you make me your partner?
Yeah, that's possible.
Tell me, what is my share?
The thing is...
- No, you fix my share first.
Let me tell you the matter.
- We will fight, fix my share.
Tell him something.
I will tell you, fifty-fifty.
Are you okay with it?
- Yes.
Then, deal.
- Done.
I'll tell you how it runs.
If you have a person's name, phone
number, address, and e-mail Id,
you will get four rupees, okay?
If you have the same person's
account number and pan card,
you will get eight rupees, okay?
What the corporates want is Data.
So, we provide it for them,
what use we have with it?
Can you ask your uncle
to arrange ten systems?
Which uncle?
Yes... I can.
You will need some twenty girls.
What are these girls for?
Can you arrange them?
His uncle will arrange all those.
You tell me the matter.
If yes, we can play the naughty boss,
on a revolving chair.
Very nice!
Isn't it fun... To simply
lounge on a chair?
The data we collect, right?
Who will we give the data to?
Pay for my tea.
Take it from my share.
It's from here, the data needed
for builders, car dealers,
private hospitals, schools,
colleges, travel agencies,
and other business enterprises
in Kerala are sent.
They are sent outside Kerala
as well, through co-coordinators.
That's more money.
Buddy, what about my share?
Share is okay.
- We will set it up.
Okay, then have it.
We send the data to this address
via courier.
They are again passed on
via. inter-state lorries.
Sir, what you said is right.
Once Kolamedu was famous
for theft and robbery.
They used to lie low in the
Bangalore-Coimbatore highways,
and rob the vehicles coming along...
That's been their
job for generations.
In 2002, when Ms Jayalalitha
was in power,
there were raids in Kolamedu.
A lot of them were
arrested back then.
To an extent, Kolamedu had
stopped being a notorious place.
Many of them were sent to quarters.
Later, nearly two hundred people
were given education.
But when they got an education, their
mode of theft changed.
They understood what
they can do with technology.
Since then,
all the crimes reported,
from Kolamedu are Cyber Crimes.
From 2012 onwards,
a lot of Cybercrimes have,
being reported from Kolamedu.
They are not big
hackers or anything.
But with the available data,
they call up people, convince
them in a short time,
and steal money from them.
'You must have received
an OTP. Can you check...?
They don't fear anything or anyone.
They know that they won't have
anything to eat, if they have fear.
There is only one reason for
crimes and revolutions...
That's hunger.
Data is their primary requirement.
They get it through various sources.
That can be coupons,
photo copy of ID cards,
or it can be any of the content
we post on online platforms.
Irrespective of gender,
they are frauds.
The master brain behind forty per cent of Cyber
crimes in South India is Kolamedu.
If we are not vigilant,
Kolamedu is as dangerous
as Jamtara in North India.
Being such a notorious place,
it's impossible to lock someone
up through an operation.
Even if you do it,
you won't be able
to cross Tamilnadu.
See,
we have tracked the IP address from
which Alphonsa received the mail.
It's from a server called Go daddy,
they bought that domain.
I had spoken to a technical
assistant from Go daddy.
They have forwarded an
IP address to us.
I have checked the details.
That's a Hyderabad based SIM.
Sir, we have got the call details.
But when we tracked the IMEA of the
phone in which the SIM had been,
this phone has been active in
Selam-Bharmapuri region,
for the last four months using
another phone number.
I'll put the details on our
WhatsApp group.
Sir.
Who is Aravind?
It's me.
Who are you?
- Oh, you're a Mallu, huh?
Just a minute.
Can you come out?
Tell me, what's the matter?
Brother, that is... We want
to create a website.
No problem, we can do it.
But there's a complication in it.
Nobody should be able
to track its IP address,
No, we will not do that.
Please, please, please, brother...
Don't go, please don't say that.
We will pay you well,
please...
Please do it for us, brother.
Come on, brother.
It is risky.
The police will easily
track the IP address.
If the police catch us,
it's going to be hell.
We know you do this,
that's why we're here.
You will have no problem
because of this, brother.
We can pay you any amount
of money you need.
How much?
You may tell…
Forty?
Possible?
- I...
Okay, brother, forty thousand is fine.
What kind of website do you need?
Tell me.
Brother, there's a hospital
in Ireland called Supernova.
Its website...
No, that's not possible.
- It's nothing, dear.
Just change the 'V' to 'W'.
That's all.
Who're you?
- Just to knock over a few nurses.
Come on...
- No, brother.
Come on, let's go over a few...
We will pay you well.
Stop there.
We know the number using
which you accessed the domain.
We have the evidence
for all the frauds,
You have been committing on
mobile and laptop,
since dropping out of
Srikrishna College, Hyderabad.
You don't know the Kerala Police.
We know how to make
you speak the truth.
Isn't because he
doesn't know us?
Joy, I don't think this will
be necessary. He will confess.
Tell me, brother.
I just created a website for them.
I don't know anything else.
For whom? Tell me...
Tell me, I say.
Just spit it out, you...
'Simbon, a fraudster
in Kolamedu Colony.'
'He eked out a living by uploading
hidden videos in porn sites.'
'There's a case against him
regarding the same.'
'He is Michael.'
'Everyone calls him, 'Vellayan'.'
'His plus point is his physique.'
'Simbon is his main helper.'
'Michael is the one who
plans everything.'
'And Simbon arranges people.'
'Execution is carried out
by his wife, Jaya.'
'They are the people who
sell lies for their living.'
'It's very difficult to win
against them.'
Antony, you should be careful.
The phone should never
get disconnected.
Basheer,
I'll take care of this,
you leave.
Catching someone inside
the colony is not that easy.
Once you are inside the colony,
you should be very alert.
Your fear doesn't show up
on your eyes.
Once you are there,
the game is yours.
Nothing should go out of our plans.
Aneesh, Mark 2, be alert.
It's nothing, brother.
But a matter of changing
a loop in a Java code.
We do coding work in a
company in Tamilnadu.
Which company?
- MCS.
In Chennai.
Where in Chennai?
- In Tea Nagar.
Okay, tell me the plan.
The plan is, there are 223 accounts.
We are going to withdraw one lakh
each from these accounts,
between 2 am to 3 am.
But, we need an account to
keep the amount safe.
Nobody should be able
to track this account.
How much will you pay us?
- You may tell, brother.
Can you give fifty...?
Okay, that's fine.
We can do it.
Will it become a problem later?
Is it safe?
You needn't worry about anything.
We will send the amount you give
to various accounts abroad.
We have more than twenty accounts
of our people there.
Okay.
- Once the deal is over,
the money will come to
your account safely.
When are you going to do it?
Probably next week, brother.
Next week... Let me see.
Hey, come here.
- Sir.
Are they your acquaintance?
If you show them to us,
we will make sure that you
are out of harm's way.
Speak up.
At least, you're a Mallu, right?
Show some loyalty to your folks.
Yes, I know them.
'Step one.'
'They sell lies for a living.'
'So, we also need to tell lies
to win against them.'
'If you carry fear in your heart...'
'You become one among them.'
'We will be there around you.'
'Just at a striking distance.'
Ravi, you cover that side.
You be here. Let me talk
to him, and come.
Michael! Hey Michael!
- Brother, let's go.
If they catch us, they will
not leave us alive.
What?
- I told you, right?
Have they come?
- They are here.
They will kill us.
Who? Who are those guys?
They are the party.
Did you brief them about
our conditions?
Yes. All okay.
They agreed?
- I told them.
Can we trust them?
- Yes. Come! You lock the door.
'Once you meet Michael,'
'you should bring him
out of the colony,'
'pretending to talk about the deal.'
Come, let's talk.
Hey!
Who are you?
Police, huh?
You have put a conference
call and all, huh?
Are you trying to cheat us?
If you are sure, you will get caught...
Dasan...
Hey, Michael.
Come on, run...
Stop there! Muthu!
Sarvana! Catch them!
They are running away. Catch them.
- Come on, man.
Look there!
- This side!
Sir, they are trapped,
get the vehicle here.
'The moment you decide
not to get killed,'
'is the moment we start winning...'
'We must play beyond
their expectation.'
'They must be horrified at
every twist we create.'
Stop.
'Step two.'
'Lure the lone wolf into our trap.'
- Catch him!
'They come unaware of the trap,'
'that is set by the one and
only Kerala Police.'
'Does anyone think that the
Kerala police is worthless?'
Sir, Mark 2.
I'm at Mark 2, come
with the vehicle.
Catch him.
Get in, you swine. Take him in.
Take the vehicle, move.
Punch him!
- Tie him up.
Stay still, rascal!
Sir, Antony has not gotten in.
He will manage himself.
Don't stop the vehicle.
Go fast.
Sir, stop the vehicle.
Hey Dasan... Open the door.
Open the door!
- Anthony!
Get in! Come on!
Get him inside the van.
Get into the van!
- Antony, come on...
Come on! Get in!
Let's go, sir.
You scoundrel! Come this side.
'Life just taught now is a lesson.'
'The moment you decide
not to give up...'
'is the moment you start winning.'
'The society measures success
of a person by his job.'
'When rich or poor comes
to Cyber Cell and cry...'
'There is one question to which
we don't get an answer.'
'What is right among these?'
The Cyber Forensic report
came last week.
It's in Janaki's favour.
But... Since it was not acceptable
to her daughter and family...
When I saw her crying in front
of our sirs...
I felt really bad.
That's why I decided to come
and say it, though it's late.
Dear girl, that video is not hers.
I don't want to hear anything.
- Just a minute, let me say a thing.
It was a few years back.
A few girls from St. Teresa's
college went on a trip to Ooty.
There was a guy there,
a room boy...
He took the video of
a girl while bathing,
using a candid camera,
and made it viral.
There was no WhatsApp
or Facebook back then.
Still, people watched it on their
small phones.
It was in 2010.
You would have read it in
newspapers.
That girl...
She jumped from
the college building.
She died.
She was my sister.
My elder sister.
Dear girl,
I know the pain of
being left alone.
You should call your mom back.
I'm leaving.
The tea is awesome.
Have it.
Where were you? How long
have I been calling you?
Why aren't you picking my calls?
I want to tell you something.
What is it?
Did anyone else trick you?
How much money did you lose?
A marriage proposal has come for me.
He is in Canada.
He is older to me.
Still, they have promised
me a nursing job there.
I had spoken about
you in my family.
But, my dad is not able to accept a
guy with a temporary job.
What should I do now?
You do whatever you
feel is good for you.
Where is your better half?
Your friend!
I don't know, sir.
What did you say?
How could you give it a miss?
Is it at your whims and fancies,
you come for the duty shift?
Just good at buttering
your seniors.
A bunch of temporary-beggars.
And there are a few officers
to entertain them.
Sir, if at all you want to say
something, say it on my face.
Don't mutter, instead.
What?
What did you say?
If I tell it on your face,
will you f**k me up?
Yes, I might do it.
It's been some time since you
have been at odds with us.
What are you itching
for when you see us?
You don't have to stop my itching.
Who the hell are you?
It's been some time... Why
do you always scorn us?
My office, I will talk
whatever I wish.
What will you talk?
- Pass the test and get the job
instead of wooing the officers, and...
- Basheer.
Stop it.
This is not a place to
massage your ego.
This is the Cyber Cell.
- He is messing with me.
Enough, stop it.
I told you already.
Antony, you come here.
I have saved another
ploy for you.
What's all these, dear?
Sir, who are we in here?
What we are doing is
also, a job, right?
Why is he showing partiality
in the workplace?
Sit here.
Dear, what's your problem?
I'm fed up, sir.
When she found a guy in Canada,
I became 'temporary' for her.
This has been my life...
I have been 'temporary'
everywhere.
Dear, this is not the actual life.
This is not love, either.
Let people who want
to go just go.
How old are you?
Twenty five years!
Whatever you see from your 15-25
years of age would be temporary.
You know, I was 26 years old when I
wrote my first PSC test.
In the examination hall,
there was a girl next to my bench,
writing the examination.
A very nice girl.
I kept looking at her
for a long time.
She was doing a lot
of mental calculation,
and writing so seriously.
I prayed in the hall,
that if at all I marry,
I must marry a girl like her.
After the examination,
I waited for her in the verandah.
Just to see her, to talk to her...
Can you imagine what I saw?
Her dad was coming out,
carrying her all by himself.
I realised her lower
body is paralysed,
I felt a respect for her.
That respect is what
is called love.
Joy, did you leave the office?
No, I haven't left yet.
Did you buy Mom's medicine?
I will come only after
buying the medicine.
Do you know the name of
the medicine?
That's for mom to eat
tonight, right? - 'Yes.'
Has mom slept?
- 'Have you taken the prescription?'
No, I have the prescription with me.
'Why do you make it late?'
- I got tied up talking to him.
'Don't get too late, okay?'
I'm leaving.
- 'Okay.'
I'm leaving, okay?
- 'Did you eat anything?'
No, I'll eat only after
coming home.
Okay, then.
Antony, did you eat anything?
No, sir I will eat.
I'll order it for you.
Eat first, and then start your duty.
Good night.
'Honey, did you eat anything?'
No, mom, I just got home.
'You should have cooked something?'
I'm too tired to cook now.
I ordered food.
'Listen, you and Alby will come
on Saturday, right?'
Let me see if we can
come on Saturday.
Alby's leave is still not confirmed.
'What's wrong?'
A cockroach jumped out
from the fridge.
'Oh, is that all?'
I got scared.
'Grandpa was telling me about
Ancy's marriage.'
'Most probably, it will be conducted
before Easter.'
'Is it Alby's time home?'
He told me that
he would be late today.
'Dear, when Alby comes, remind
him of our LIC thing.'
Shucks! One minute mom...
I'll call you back.
'What happened?'
- Our electricity went out.
'Control Bravo 18.'
'Bravo 18 control answering, sir.'
'Can you tell us the exact location
where the incident happened?'
'Sir, opposite Chaitram
Textiles, Irumbanam.'
'On the way to the colony,'
'close to the flat seen
on the right side.'
'The guards are
waiting over there. '
Sir.
'You must do something.'
'You must locate yourself so
that none of their folks,'
'enter the room where
the incident has happened.'
What's the status?
The inquiry is on.
- What?
Who are you?
- My name is Johnson.
Which flat do you occupy?
I'm the care taker in here.
Take out the register.
Hey, there is no recording in it?
Usually, no one from
outside comes here.
So, is the guy who came just
now, your acquaintance?
Oh, my Gosh!
That's not it, sir.
What is your name?
- Sunil.
What?
Where's your house?
At Irumbaram, sir.
Where in Irumbaram?
Under... Under the bridge.
How long have you been here?
Around... around four years.
Who is Joseph?
It's me, sir.
When did your duty get over?
At 9 o'clock, Sir.
I left early today.
My wife had called me saying
our kid was sick.
That's why I left home early.
When did you get
into your duty?
I... I got late, sir.
What time, I'm asking.
Might be around... 11 o'clock.
So, you knew that there would be
no one here after 9 o'clock.
Geez! That's not it.
That's not it, sir.
- Then?
I mean...
Hey, are you drunk?
- No, sir.
You come with me.
Let me ask you...
I'm not drunk, sir.
Joseph.
Is it your church name?
Yes, sir.
What happened to the generator here?
- It gets busted, off and on.
Don't you have an association here?
Yes, sir. He is the secretary.
What is your name?
- My name's Paul.
Who are you?
- The Treasurer.
Name?
- Ashley.
Who is the lady's neighbour?
It's him.
- It's me.
Where were you when
the incident took place?
I was sleeping in my flat.
Where else am I supposed to go?
Smart!
Hey, you need not ask questions,
just answers will do.
What happened to the generator?
The diesel got over.
We have sent someone to buy
diesel, sir. He will come soon.
Did you take the CCTV
footage in here?
They have CCTV's.
But none of them are working.
No generator, no CCTV...
What association...
Thank God!
You, at least, have a generator.
Allow these people to go only
after collecting their details.
Why do you want my details?
What wrong did I do?
Something bizarre happens in
your flat, on your floor,
and you, the secretary, knows
nothing about it.
Do you get it?
You are not the
Chief Secretary, right?
My details needed?
Yes, give it to them in
writing and then leave.
What's up?
Sir, there's no rape attempt
or anything.
The motive is theft.
The lady's jewellery
has been stolen.
Sir, here's the lift.
- Let's walk up the stairs.
How's the lady now?
They admitted her in
the Medical Trust hospital,
as she has a blood clot behind
her head from the hit.
Did you inform her husband?
It's her husband and her friends
who admitted her to the hospital.
Are any of our people
accompanying them? - Yes, sir.
Promod and Rajesh are
there in the hospital.
Ask them to update us
with every single thing.
Okay, sir.
Sir, it's over there.
I should never see you again
wearing this helmet of yours.
If you repeat this, I'll call your
customer care and give a complaint.
It's over there, sir.
Sir, it's from here she
was attacked first.
They must have dragged her out
this way...
A heavy tool must have been
employed to hit her.
That's why a lot of blood
has been lost.
We have noted it in the report.
Have you got any clue regarding
the weapon used for the crime?
Sir, it should be something
like an iron rod.
Okay, I'm here at the crime spot.
Yes, yes, sir is here.
I'll tell him.
Sir, there was a call
from the hospital.
He is on ventilator.
- Is it?
Did you collect the left impression?
Sure! You stay there.
Are the ridges clear?
- No, Sir.
What if we look for
any vertical pattern?
He has stolen everything,
he could take.
We have collected the
finger prints.
What about her husband's details?
Alby, he's working in Info-park.
'Sruthi, tell me.'
Alby, did you leave from office?
'No, I told you, right?
That project of mine...'
'What's it, dear?'
Can you come over here fast?
'What happened?
Tell me the matter.'
Here, the electricity has gone out.
Why can't they switch on
the generator?
This has become a routine
these days.
'Dear Sruthi, what's the use of
calling me and saying all these?'
'You call the security,
and tell the matter.'
I don't know...
I'm getting scared.
'What for?'
'You have food and go to bed.
I'll be there soon.'
It's for saying that I called you.
I had ordered food online.
You should have seen
the aggression of the delivery boy.
'What happened?'
- He was wearing a helmet.
Haven't we told the association
several times,
not to let people
wearing helmet inside?
'Dear, isn't the security down?'
'Sunil or Joseph
who's on duty today?'
Let me check.
Don't hang up.
'No, I won't.'
'Why are you so tense?'
I'll call you back, okay?
'What's the problem?'
- He's not gone until now.
'Who are you talking about?'
Sir.
Sir, we found a phone.
'Control Bravo 18.'
'Bravo control answering,
Sir. Over!'
'We have found a mobile phone from
the location, quite suspiciously.'
'Please send someone from
Cyber Cell to the location,'
'for collecting the
details of the same.'
'Control answering clear, sir.
Over!'
How long since I asked you here?
Sir...
For a case like this,
don't you have permanent
employees in the Cyber Cell?
Sir, the phone has been switched on.
Do I have to open the phone-lock?
Sorry, sir.
What an arrogant man!
Let's open the phone-lock.
Dude, it's not...
N...MM...
Hello.
Alby, have you reached?
Oh, friends are there too?
Should I come down?
Food is here... but...
we will share anyway...
Sir.
We have unlocked the phone.
Sir, we have some findings.
Shall we tell?
Findings?
What findings?
Sir, the lady spoke to her mom,
from 9.57 to 10.07 pm.
That has been recorded
in the phone.
She says that she has
ordered food online.
That is when the power goes.
Sir, after that... at 10.12 pm...
she talked to her husband.
That too has been recorded
in the phone.
'Why do you feel scared? Have
dinner and go to sleep. I'll come.'
'Honey, I called to talk to you
about it. I ordered food online.'
'You must have seen the
delivery guy. - What's wrong?
If our calculation is right...
The theft took place between
10.20 - 10.30 pm,
Find out who made
the food delivery here,
and collect his details.
- Sir.
I'll take the delivery boy's number.
Sanjiv sir.
I'm calling from the crime-spot.
I have sent you a number on WhatsApp.
Can you get me the
details of the same?
I'll track it down, and
call you soon.
Sir, please take the network
details of this number.
Sajiv sir.
- Antony.
I have tracked down the details
of the number you sent.
The number is switched off
right now.
Can you at least
send me the call list?
'The suspect's phone
is switched off.'
'When we inquired about
his history,'
'it seems like he's involved
in a few other crimes too.'
'The last call he made to a
number was at 11.15 pm.'
'The present tower location
of the number he called is,'
'Angamaly-Aluva road.
Sir, over!'
Dear hubby, my head's
aching like hell.
A vehicle is following us.
Is it a police vehicle, hubby?
Come outside.
- What is it, sir?
Just get out.
- What's the matter, sir?
How are you related to Dany?
Which Dany, sir?
Which Dany?
You have spoken to him twice
in the last one hour.
Also chatted on WhatsApp.
Where is he right now?
Sir, I guess, you got me wrong.
I don't know this Dany.
This question is not
meant for you.
Tell me, madam.
Where is this Dany?
Why is he always talking to you?
I know him...
How do you know him?
He is a friend's brother.
- Which friend?
Kavitha David.
She and I were batchmates
in college.
What's the affair between you
and your batch mate's brother?
Love?
No, sir... No.
Or any other extra
curricular activities?
It's nothing like that.
Then?
He messages
and calls once in a while.
We are friends.
Okay.
What did he tell you when he
spoke to you for the last time?
He asked me if I can book
him a ticket to Mangalore.
For what?
- Just look for the train time.
I just know that there's
something wrong.
And not the details...
Did you book him the tickets?
No, sir.
He told he will go by bus.
Sir, there's a Kollur-Mookambika bus
from Ernakulam stand at 2.30.
That goes via. Mangalore.
Has the Mookambika bus going
via Mangalore reached?
No, sir. It's running late, today.
How long will it take?
- Another half an hour or more.
Sir, he might have gone
to the other side.
Hey, what's your name?
Sir, shall we check the CCTV
footage here?
Okay.
Sir, is there an exit that side?
Just show the lights there.
The railway police is there.
So, he won't go that way.
Just show the Cam B.
- Please zoom it.
He's the one...
- Wait, just pause.
Yes, sir.
See...
Is he the one?
Zoom it, please.
- Dasan, we found him.
Is he anywhere there?
- No, sir.
Sir, we found the guy.
He is there.
You are Dany, right?
Let's go?
What?
Stop there.
- Catch him.
Hold him!
- Sir, I have reformed now.
Sir, I'm telling you. I'm not my
old self.
Sir, please listen to me.
Let me go.
- Stay quiet.
Why did you catch me now?
Sir, please don't...
- You better confess...
Sir, I don't know anything.
Sir, I swear, I don't know anything.
- Check his mobile, sir.
I swear upon my mom,
I don't know anything, sir.
He knows everything,
just ask him, sir.
We have got proof confirming
that you have done it.
Don't try to make a
fool out of us.
Do you hear it?
I don't know anything about it.
We have got A-Z details of
your chat with your aunt.
Tell me the truth.
Tell me.
Tell me, you scumbag.
I'll tell you everything.
I'll say it...
I had indeed gone to the
flat to deliver food.
But when I went there, I saw an
ambulance and a huge crowd.
When I asked a guy about it,
he told me that,
a lady from the flat,
I had gone to,
deliver food has been
attacked by someone.
So, I didn't stay there any longer.
And, at the same time, I got a
food order from Vennala.
So, I went to Kakkanad, collected
food, and went directly to Vennala.
I go there often.
I know the old couple over
there very well.
But when I went there,
what I saw was...
Madam.
Trust me, sir!
I don't know anything else.
Get him out.
Just get out, you...
Get walking.
Sir, please tell him.
Sir.
Sir, I don't know anything.
Sir, please don't trap me in it.
Sir.
No, sir.
She is dead.
Sir, here he is.
'Control Bravo Team!'
- 'Control Bravo responding.'
'The accused has confessed
to murdering,'
'an additional person in the second
house from the church in Venella.'
'Send the officer in-charge?'
'Yes, sir.'
'You mentioned the second
house from the Church at Venella'
'It's clear, sir. I'll inform.'
- 'Control Bravo!'
'We're sending two corpses
recovered from Venella.'
'Call me once you see it.'
This is also a theft, sir.
He has snatched the jewels
from the old lady.
It is definitely him.
He's trying to fool us.
Does he have any family
or relatives here?
Sir.
- None, sir.
The woman in the flat is dead, sir.
Rayeesha called.
We have got a few details
from her phone.
It is at 10.30 pm, she
has placed the order.
From the testimony we
got from the flat,
it is at 10.30 pm that lady
was taken to the hospital.
Given the details,
it's possible that,
Dany collected food from
the hotel at 10.15.
If that is true,
who delivered food to her,
in between the calls she made
to her mom and her husband?
From the time of the attack, and
the time that Dany said,
chances are less that he
did the crime.
Sir, Irumbanam-Vennala...
Numbers common to
these two towers...
'Common numbers?'
- Yes, I need the list of,
common numbers that fall under
Irumbanam-Vennala towers.
In both of the crime scenes,
we don't have any other common
link other than Dany.
Sir, he has committed
both the crimes.
He's simply making a
fool out of us.
But, these guys say that
it's not him.
Alright, please send all the
details on WhatsApp.
'I have sent it in our group.'
- Okay, thanks.
Sir, between the stipulated time,
There is a number, active under both
Irumbanam and Vennala towers.
Later, it was moving…
I have taken the details
of the number.
The number got switched off
at Kalamassery.
That is in the name of a lady.
Kavitha David.
Give me his mobile phone.
What is the number, you said?
8281...
- 8281...
91...
- 5667.
Who is this?
Sir, she is my sister.
- Your sister?
Are you both messing with us?
What is this, sir?
- Where is she?
She is at her house.
- Place?
Sir... Sir, Kalamassery.
Kalamassery.
Sir, my nephew
won't be asleep.
Sir, he will get scared.
Please, sir.
Zip your mouth, you...
We are cops.
Open the door!
Two of you go to the back door.
What's the matter, sir?
Kavitha David?
That's me.
What's the matter?
How did your phone number,
come under Irumbanam-Vennala
mobile tower last night,
between 10 -11.15.
I don't know, sir.
I hardly use my phone
because I'm carrying.
It's my husband who uses
my phone these days.
Where is your husband?
What is your name?
Jhony.
Where were you last night?
I was here.
Some people have seen you
around Irumbanam-Vennala at 10.00 pm.
No, sir. He was here at home
from 8.00 pm yesterday.
He has not gone anywhere.
Sir, I was here only.
I was watching cricket on the TV.
And, I slept around 12-12.30.
Where did you go just now?
I had gone to see off someone
at the bus stand.
Who's that?
- My brother, Jakes.
He was here for the last one week.
He's working in Technopark,
Thiruvananthapuram.
He was...? What about now?
Dear, sir, no one is sure
about his things.
He was working in
a call centre there.
His salary was very less.
But his lifestyle is that
of a rich guy.
He has not been getting a salary
for the past 3-4 months.
That's what he said.
He has taken some
money from me.
How much?
- Around two and a half lakhs.
Last day, he quarrelled with
me as I asked for my money.
Was he out of the house
last night?
He comes and goes at odd hours.
He comes home at midnight and all.
What I asked is about
the last night?
He was out last night.
It was around 12-12.30 am
when we reached back.
Does he use this scooter?
Yes, he uses it when
he comes here.
What about your sister's mobile?
He was using her mobile
phone this time,
saying that his SIM card
is blocked.
Take down the details.
- Okay, sir.
It's both of you together
doing all these, right?
No, sir. Please trust me.
True that he had come
to my room.
He comes with a huge
list of impossible plans.
What plan?
He has loaned money from
a girl who works with him.
He has invested it in a money
chain like Bitcoin or something.
Now, the girl is after him
asking for her money...
Her husband has filed a
police case against him.
If you are not together,
how is he able to get to all
places before you reach there?
That's what even I
don't understand?
He had indeed come with
me that day to deliver food.
For what?
He was so adamant about
coming with me.
Why did you take him
along with you?
He was so adamant about
coming with me.
I took him along just to save him
from getting bored of sitting alone.
My dear, sir, I don't know
anything other than this.
Don't know, means?
Please trust me, sir.
Can we check Dany's phone
once more?
In which office is he working?
In Techno Park.
Hey, this is a problematic App.
Let me search for it.
Did you see him today?
- No, sir, I haven't.
Did he call or message you today?
- Sir.
An unauthorized
App called Mobile Spy,
has been installed on this phone.
The person who has installed
the app in this phone,
can access all the Apps in this
phone via another phone.
For example, Facebook,
WhatsApp...etc.
Jakes, what are you doing with
my phone all the time?
Dude, you keep aside all your
unworkable plans,
and start doing some job like this.
You will get quite a good salary.
Which bus did you see him off?
The Thiruvananthapuram bus, sir.
'Bravo 18 responding.'
- 'Noted!'
'A boy aged between
18 and 25 years has boarded,'
'the super-fast bus from Aluva
to Thiruvananthapuram...'
Hello, KSRTC here!
Sir, this is from Cyber Cell, Kochi.
There's something urgent
regarding a case.
Sir, I need the number of either
the driver or the conductor of the,
Thiruvananthapuram super-fast bus
that left at 4.00 am from the stand.
I want it now, it's urgent.
Sir, what's Ajayan's number... Who's
gone in the Thiruvananthapuram bus?
This is from Cyber Cell, Kochi.
- Cyber Cell?
Sir, don't panic.
We have information
that a suspect related to,
a murder case in Kochi
has boarded your bus.
We need to know about it.
This vehicle?
- Yes, yes.
We will send the photo
on WhatsApp.
Can you see if he's there
inside the bus...
You need not hang up the call.
- I'll call you back, sir.
Can you check that photo
and tell me?
Okay.
Hey, hello.
Ask him, what's it?
Sir.
No such man is there
inside this vehicle.
You must have gotten
the wrong bus.
Okay, sir.
- Okay, alright.
Sir.
- Sir.
He is not on the bus,
said the conductor.
Maybe he got into another
bus in between.
Sir, we had called
up Aluva stand,
and had taken the number of
the KSRTC conductor.
There's no such a man
in the bus, it seems.
Maybe he got into another
bus in between.
Hey, he's calling back. Hello.
'Sir, he's there inside the bus.'
'Come fast!'
Sir, he's there inside
the bus, it seems.
Where did he go?
Towards that side.
We couldn't catch him.
Downwards...
Get the vehicle down.
- Come on, fast.
Come on, sir.
He won't go beyond this, sir.
It's a swamp over there.
Sir, be careful.
- Show the lights towards there.
There will be snakes over there.
It's a swamp, no place
beyond this to run.
Sir, we can hear some
sound from there.
He must be somewhere here. Come!
Sir, the gate is lying open.
He has gone this way for sure.
See, the gate is open.
He must be somewhere inside this.
Do one thing.
Both of you, go that side.
- Okay, sir.
You, towards that side. Go.
Watch your way and go.
Be careful.
You go that way.
Is he over there, Danesh?
How dare you?
Damn! Leave me.
Sir...
Sir, please come.
- Leave me.
Antony...
You go catch him.
Sir...
- What is it?
Are you hurt?
- What did he run?
He ran towards that side.
Sir, we got him. Come fast.
Stop there!
- Sir...
Sir!
Thrash him, sir.
Are you playing with cops?
Don't wriggle, you idiot!
Are you trying to make
a fool out of us?
Please leave me, sir.
Wahab.
Get up, and stand straight.
Stand up.
Stand straight, I say!
Sir, please...
- Come on.
Walk, fast.
Is it locked from inside?
Drag him inside.
Did you think you can
make a fool out of us?
Get inside, all of you.
I got in, sir.
Did they get in?
What's their name?
Hey, show me your hands.
Let me see.
Yes, sir.
How is your hand?
- That's okay, sir.
Get into the vehicle.
We will drive you to the hospital.
No, sir...we have a bike...
We will go by ourselves.
What is your name?
Antony.
Vinay Dasan.
Okay, sir. Thank you, sir.
Come on in.
Good morning, sir.
- Good morning.
Did you go to the hospital?
- Yes, we did.
Dasan.
What is your plan?
Nothing, we want to sleep
for some time.
You should give us a
day's leave, okay?
My body hurts.
That's not it.
I asked you about your
plans.
Just go on... like this...
Joy. Please come here.
You want a smoke?
- No.
No, sir.
How long can you continue doing
a worthless job like this?
The government has
decided to lay off,
temporary employees
from KSRTC and KSEB.
It's the same here as well.
Isn't it?
Are you sending us away?
Secure your life somewhere else,
without getting insulted here.
Go.
- Dear, sir...
We love working here, sir.
We will somehow stay here.
We don't want any salary.
Please. Sir.
Dear, you can't...
It's an order from the government.
Sir.
You go, dear.
It's nothing, but...
We will become a zero
in front of everyone.
That's why.
This is the nature of our system.
Go and find something better.
You may go.
Sir...
'In life, there's a blockade
everywhere, isn't it?'
'Only those blocked
somewhere have succeeded in life.'
'Fresh proverb, huh?'
'Where did you get it from?'
'My friend who's a moron told me.'
'But, that's true.'
'Get lost, brat!'